with dignity worthy hello resume
достойно достойно дравствуйте резюме
blog I'm a blogger just for the same good and
блоге я блоггер просто на то же блага и
I'm not a blogger usually threw off jamming blogger
я не блогер обычно скинул глушим блогера
damn it I bought them still God knows when
блин я их купил еще черт знает когда
comfortable headphones are just wireless
удобные наушники просто они беспроводные
around the house when you go to music you listen
по дому когда ходишь музыку слушаешь
comfortably look I'm from ukraine the city of
удобно смотрите я из украины город
khmelnitsky and where are you from
хмельницкий а вы откуда из россии
I am from Lugansk, the people's city of Stakhanov,
я с луганска народной город стаханов а
namely, with fear,
именно с со страхом
you can only confirm that you are from there,
можете только подтвердить что вы оттуда
because many simply from Russia do
потому что многие просто из россии
not seem to be enough, it's interesting, I look, I
недостаточно вот интересно я смотрите я
write it down so that is, I can then
записываю так то есть я могу потом
post this video and if something
выложить этот ролик и если что-то там
cannot be said better there  not to
нельзя говорить лучше не говорить
speak obediently interesting here you are as a resident,
вот послушно интересно вот вы как житель
that is, you are now where to be
то есть вы сейчас находитесь где быть
directly
непосредственно
yourself in the city, but how do you feel about the
себя в городе а вот как вы относитесь к
war between Russia and Ukraine now on the
войне россии с украиной сейчас на
territory, then there is no war,
территорию то нет никакой войны господи
Lord, what to talk about there is a special operation on 8
о чем говорить есть спецоперация по 8
scale opal conquered to find out what  this
опал масштаба завоевана узнать что это
is what
такое
it is when bombers fly to be
это когда летят бомбардировщики быть
completely cities sparing no civilians
полностью города не жалея ни мирных
then stick out yourself and now
никого после торчите себя а сейчас
something is Mariupol Severodonetsk it’s not a
что-то мариуполь северодонецка ней не
gang you’ll open normally
банда нормально вскроешь строятся
Mariupol kind of didn’t bomb
мариуполе рода не бомбили
shelling let’s see how you live
артобстрела давайте вот вы как жить вы
you introduce yourself as a resident of the LC so
вы представляетесь как житель лнр так
you can tell me then because the Russian
можете мне тогда потому что мне русские
whales tell me fairy tales out you as a
кита сказки рассказывают out вы как
direct citizen of Ukraine
непосредственный гражданин украины
who  and now a citizen of Ukraine will come out
который и сейчас выйдет гражданин
because you
украины потому что вы паспарту
can tell me the passe-partout of indicators, but how and
показателей можете мне сказать а как и
when by whom the LC was proclaimed what kind of
когда кем была провозглашена лнр каким
people you didn’t become, you can tell the
народа not стали можете рассказать
story of the knife was after all, after all, a
историю нож было все-таки как-никак
referendum a referendum this is what you can
референдум референдум этов какие можете
referendum date I know I don’t
дату референдума на знаю я точно не
remember exactly anymore  14 + either it's May May
помню больше 14 + либо это май май
really, I'm really, let's
правда я ну правда давайте я сейчас
just hide it, it was May, this is important,
точно скрыто было мая это это важно
because from what date you can
потому что с какого числа у вас можете
tell when you started
сказать когда у вас начались боевые
hostilities like this,
действия вот так
but the first combat we have started
но первый боевой есть у нас начались
March March we arrived for the first time  do not
март мартик нам первый раз приехал не не
look now
смотри сейчас
deferent so you were 2 no
деферентом так вас был 2 нет
referendum one of there aida November 14
референдум один из там aida 14 ноября
if mother mo  can you tell me where
если мать можете рассказать где вот
Luhansk and Alchevsk would be and
луганский и алчевский какие были бы и
who died in March,
кто погиб в марте
but I won’t say so, to be honest, the
но он так не скажу честно говоря
Lugansk Republic from your young
луганская республику от вашей молодой
gazur look and at that time I was
газур смотреть и я на тот момент у я был
in the Crimea,
в крыму
I
я с 13 по
was in the Crimea military on  you
16 год был в крыму военные на вы
already know how, I didn’t serve once, too, the archers
уже умеет я не служил раз тоже лучников
lived, I understood it, it’s just that you look at
жил понял на просто получается смотрите
me, no one rolls you arrived, so you
мне никто булок вы приехали так вот вы
now live in the PRC, you name it and the LPR,
сейчас живете в кнр вы называете и лнр
you can then tell me here is the date of
вы мне можете тогда сказать вот дату
creation of Elena and who created the
создания елена и кто его создал
referendum, you are the one who he already is  was
референдума ты тот который он уже был
when there was already an occupation, there were already
когда уже была оккупация уже были
hostilities if the beekeeper
военные действия если часов пасечник и
was there, well, this question is being cooled, that's
были ну это вопрос охлаждают вот вот
it, and by the way, it’s very interesting to me that
именно и мне кстати очень интересно что
you were caught as a citizen of the LPR for Russian
вы попались как гражданин лнр за русские
fairy tales, but how would you know,
сказки рассказывают а вы как бы знаете
here I am, for example, if you ask me
вот я например если меня спрашивать
now, wait,
сейчас подождите
well  in short, I want to say our first one, if
ну короче я хочу сказать первый наш как
not the president, who we were there and the head of the
не президента кто нас там был и глава
republic was not really, but where did he
республики был не особо а откуда он
come from, who elected him the head of the Komi Republic,
взялся кто его избрал главу республики
we voted not that  this show was
коми мы голосовали не не этого шоу это
when it was Maltsev there was
когда было мальцева не было
no no it was just a republic at first you
нет было просто республика сначала вы по
head by head then you chose to the
главу потом то выбирали
left who created the republic the people who
налево кто создал республику народ кто
as a people look look in what
как народ смотрите подыщите в какой
form it was in April since the
форме вот он был апрель месяц так как
people were
создал народ
created all the people gathered in Luhansk whether it’s like a
съехался весь народ в луганске ли ну как
bow  watch the vote as my
лук смотреть голосование как мои тоже
relative Russo acquaintances in Moscow
относительные руссо знакомые в москве
were voting in St. Petersburg there were
были голосований в питере были
votes and this vote is the same
голосования и это голосование ту же
consider it was already a
рассмотрите это уже проводился
referendum when there were
референдум когда уже были боевые
already hostilities already a lot of people
действия уже очень много людей по
left so from there who controlled the
уезжала так оттуда кто подконтрольную
body scored a signature turns out the
тела набрали сигнатурой получается
referendum was already carried out from the people  with
референдум проводили уже с людей с
people who
людьми которые
during the hostilities remained there on
во время боевых действий там остались на
this territory, they could not leave Amelie
этой территории не смогли выехать амели
in Ukraine or in Russia, that is, or you
в украине или в россии на то есть либо
didn’t want them, they didn’t want them, yes, that
не хотели вы их они не хотели да да то
is, this one and let’s say grandparents,
есть вот этот и допустим бабушки-дедушки
we didn’t call them people too  survived, that
не мы тоже их и звали люди выживали то
is, it turns out, well, here you are as a citizen of
есть получается ну вот вы как гражданин
r.  a resident, so you understand
р . житель так вы получается понимаете
that the referendum is held when there was already a
что референдум проводится когда уже
huge number of the population there
огромного количества населения там не
, though they were forced because of the
было правда они вынуждены из-за боевых
hostilities to leave either in Russia or
действий были уехать либо в россии либо
in Ukraine, who is much closer to whom where
в украину кому куда ближе у кого где
relatives are  was already in one on May 11,
рефреном это уже был в один на 11 мая
so when the population of a large large
так когда уже население больших большой
part was already there,
части уже там не было
and in April,
а в апреле
so where did someone and how they said that before
так вот откуда кто и как сказал что до
May 11, because the LC say you
11 мая потому что лнр говорят служишь
serve, it was like this, for example, in April of the world
были было так вот например в апреле мира
Turchin Turchinov when he sent windows
турчин турчинов когда окнам отправил
dobrobut look 2 on April 12, 2013
добробут смотри 2 на 12 апреля 2013 года
when
когда
this one was captured Slavyansk flexible April 12,
этот захватили славянск гибким 12 апреля
2012 Russian will be fine, by the
2012 года российский буду хорошо я
way, I understand this captured island
кстати вот это понимает захватили island
geek Girkin came in with a group of people 52
geek гиркин зашел какой группой людей 52
people, but he came out above me so
человека вот а вышел выше мне так
look well, let's go by
смотрите ну давайте так давайте по
chronology  the tank
хронологии разбираться зашел вышел танк
came out went there 52 so then they went into the throat
зашел туда 52 так потом в горловку зашли
two days later in the throat what they did in the
через два дня в горловке что сделали в
throat they killed the deputy of the Supreme Soviet
горловке убили депутата верховного
veta of the
совета
city council or to
городского совета либо к
this, I understand that this is all the action for us
это я понятно вот это все нам действие
there, I don’t understand the point is that
там не понять у меня суть в том что то
many people say that the Russian
многие говорят чтоб зашла российская
army should
армия
enter the army first went into all the same
армия пошла сначала заходить во все таки
for blah blah blah blah but let
для бла бла бла бла но давайте давайте
’s chronologically now then we pulled ourselves up
по хронологии сейчас потом подтянулись
here  these all sorts of Russian mercenaries of the
вот эти всякие там российские наемники
Cossacks were Russian Cossacks were
казачества были российские казаки были
citizens of Russia, we had ours, you can
граждане россии у нас наши были можно ко
come to me, wait, but this is the Don Cossacks,
мне ну подождите а вот это казачества
this was next, I say that
донской это дальше было я говорю что у
we had our Cossacks, we had a
нас был нас было наше казачества нас
brain day, let's be in the
мозговой дне давайте так были в
Lugansk region Cossacks with  this bathhouse to
луганской области казаки с этой бане до
the dust,
на пыль
this bearded woman, while a bunch of
баба этот бородатый тогда как куча вот
these visitors, when
этих приезжих в когда в славянск зашли
they entered Slavyansk, militants began to go there, plus they
так начали ехать туда боевики плюс
recruited local criminals there,
набирали местных там криминалитет так
for example, vision was not provided,
например не обеспечен видения было
it was goodness they were paid
работы она благости им там платили
money by someone there and shows
деньги кто-то и shows идейных
absolute ideological considerations  and also that is, there were
соображений абсолют а также то есть были
people who supported these militants
люди которые поддерживали этих боевиков
for ideological reasons, yes, but if we
из идейных соображений да но если мы
return to that  what the
возвращаемся к тому что провозгласил
people proclaimed so then let's
народ так то давайте
when and how did this people proclaim the
когда и как этот народ провозгласил
Donetsk-Luhansk people's republic a
донецка луганскую народную республику
referendum when there was one waiting for us to hand over
референдум когда был один ждет мы сдать
them
их не num1 и самая когда уже народа на
you will recognize the
какой то же опять же общее но узнаете
majority because and because they looked
большинство потому и потому что смотрели
before
до
that there was no sum I just nothing
этого не было сумме я просто ничего
during the general thing in the Lugansk region of the
во время общем штука в луганской области
scanner but 5 million donor in
сканера но миллионов 5 донор в
5 million already from death this is one
миллионов 5 уже со смерти это одна
eighth session of a kopeikin and it would not be but
восьмая сессия копейкин и было бы не но
I generally say for 14 years well  let
я вообще говорю на 14 год ну давайте
's think about how we have and maybe millions a
по идее ишь как у нас а может и миллионы
million - Donetsk is exactly billion 5 and
миллион - донецкий точно биллионов 5 и
here the population of the Lugansk region of the strip
вот население луганской области полоса
was 2 million two million people,
было 2 миллиона два миллиона людей на
and the part that the LPR announce is it
причем та часть которая лнр огласить она
is a small child, it is less than
это небольшая чадами она меньше
1 less and less well, how to wear, for example,
1 все менее ну как носи например
Starobelsky  was
старобельский был
everywhere not sick, look, he was only in
везде не тошнит смотри он был только на
those territories that were controlled
тех территориях которые контролировались
by militants,
боевиками
he could not be carried out because  there, the
он не мог проводиться потому что там
Ukrainian authorities were
украинская власть была
in Mariupol, there was a referendum, a
в мариуполь ешь был референдум
referendum, Mariupol was washed in the sea,
референдум мариуполе морил в морю по
but only there was a referendum, and
лишь был референдум а
then and then the
потом а потом уже
moment of Mariupol had already begun, I won’t say, by the
начат момент мариуполя не скажу
way, I’ll look in Mariupol at the time of
я посмотрю кстати в мариуполь на момент
this referendum, it was already again even
этого референдума он был уже опять даже
for many people, but disappeared later, but
на много людей по пропадала потом а
let’s take  for example, Starobelsk, so
возьмем например старобельск так
Starobilsk, there was a referendum in it was not
старобельск в нем был референдум не был
in the entire territory of the neckline region,
на всей территории области декольте
sun was yes, because now it was at
вск был да потому что сейчас был под
that time, in general, the front line of Debaltseve
то время вообще линия фронта дебальцево
was also provided, suppressed the front in general
тоже был предоставлен подавлял вообще
, that is, it turns out that
фронт вот то есть получается что эй
hey damn it’s a pity it’s a pity it’s a pity
блин жалко жалко жалко 6 разорвалась
and for the Russians,
дуже классное видео и для русских вот
look who they tell us so that the
смотрите которые нам рассказывают чтобы
people of the LC we don’t know when then
человек нас лнр он не знаю когда тогда
the water was created if they talk about a
создалась на вода если говорят про
referendum, the
референдум
referendum took place already during the
референдум проходил уже во время
occupation, so the eleventh and it was
оккупации так одиннадцатом а это уже
already hostilities were
было военные действия были
who then
кто тогда
on whose behalf what people proclaimed a
от чьего имени какой народ провозгласил
referendum
референдум
in April  not a referendum of the LC in April, that
в апреле не референдум лнр в апреле то
is, five dudes gathered at the  ita so the
есть собралась пять чувак у кита так
alcoholics of the windows of the medina and said that
алкоголиков окна медине и сказали что
they are now the LPR, this Vasya will be shorter, the
они теперь лнр этот вася будет короче
head herself appointed himself the head of this
глава сама назначили себя главой этом
republic and
республики и
no one elected them all, the Luhansk
все их никто не избирал был луганский
Regional Council was an absolutely legitimate
областной совет абсолютно легитимный
body that represents all the inhabitants of the
орган который представляет всех жителей
Lugansk region, it does not have any
луганской области он никакие
resolutions on independence, and so
постановления о независимости и так
on  accepted that the deputies whom
дальше не принимал что депутаты которых
you played people all the people of the Luhansk
вы играли люди все люди луганской
region they did not support this on behalf of
области они это не поддержали от имени
their voters about some five
своих избирателей о каких-то там пять
or seven or ten weirdos there so they
или семь или десять чудиков так
gathered and said shout they are now the LPR,
собрались и сказали shout они теперь лнр
but this Vasya is shorter than the head and
а вот этот вася короче глава и
with the help of such Russian mercenaries  so they
с помощью таких наемников российских так
began to seize territory, and when we
начали захватывать территорию и когда мы
talk about a referendum, the referendum
говорим про референдум референдум
was already held in the occupied
проводился уже на оккупированной
territory, when most of the population,
территории когда большей части населения
due to hostilities, was no longer part
из-за боевых действий уже не было частью
fled to Russia, part fled to Ukraine,
бежала в россию часть убежала в украину
so part remained there
так часть осталась там
what kind of
про какую
freedom of choice we are talking about and under what
свободу выбора мы говорим и при какой
legislation
законодательств
I would have announced I would have come to Dagestan
я бы объявил взял бы пришел в дагестан
skaz  in short, we are now the Dagestan
сказал короче мы теперь дагестанское
People's Republic
народная республика
started hostilities, they kicked out the police from there, in
начали боевые действия выгнали оттуда
short
короче
, the Dagestan police
полицию так дагестанскую против нас
would start fighting against us, they drove
начали бы боевые действием их согнали
people at gunpoint in the
людей под дулами автоматов на
referendum, they said here people go
референдуме сказали вот сюда люди поди
let the amount we need vst
пусть сумму нам потрибно vst
sensitivity to the ideality of the
чувствительность к идеальность
document of water still show our
документ воды таки показывать нашим
Ramadan of that  so that on other Sinai
рамаданом того чтобы на иных синайскую
what was knocked out to Russian Romans to
чего выбивалась российским римлянам
foreign Romans
иноземным римлянам
Irma is an informative tsar to him and try to
ирма ему царь информативный и пытайтесь
put like
ставьте лайк
command you even survived him to
командуйте ты даже даже выжил его для
passer the mind
пассерования виду и
and after here a kilogram in the region of
и после здесь на килограмм в области по
ukraine we will lubricate them
ukraine смажем них